Situation
  Workstations at Ross Terminals are failing from time to time.  These terminals are important because they are used for Dispatch as well as other operations functions.  Line-haul trucks connect each of the terminals with Penacook several times each night.  These line-haul runs can be used to deploy hot spare machines.

But the hot spare machines have to be configured first.

Proposal
Use two or more PC work stations.
Configure them with an operating system and several pre-requisite applications like a SQL server database
Add a set of users to each of the work stations, along with functioning ICONs to for the applications and functionality they need
Test the work stations
Deploy the work stations via line-haul for several user acceptance tests.

Going forward, manage the work stations.  Keep them up to date as users and applications change.

Work station categories
  Stand alone work station (for the VT, ME, and CT terminals) -includes a local dispatch database  -includes a Comet Tracker database as well 

  Dispatch Server work station
		--has dual monitor cards installed (for Sutton and NH )
    --has Sql server installation allow it to function as a Sutton or NH Dispatch server


Refined and documented install procedure for the Dispatch Software.
	Dispatch 1.6 software will be installed on both of these work stations by an
    automated process.
  This automated process will be documented and tested.  Creating the documentation and the automated process will ensure Ross Express combat the single-point-of-failure represented by the home-grown nature of your Dispatch software


Esimate:
   Basic work station configuration -- 2 weeks
   Automate Server and Dispatch installation -- 2 weeks
   Automate other applications (Email, ROADVISION, etc) -- 1 weeks
   Document the Dispatch program --1 week.    
   
Retainer:
	



Background


Feature  COMET TRACKER USER

   As a Comet Tracker User
	 I need the ability Examine and manipulate the vehicle tracking system.
   So that, in real time, I can see where each of my trucks actually is.

#############################################

Feature  STANDALONE DISPATCHER

   As a Standalone Dispatcher
   I need the ability to run Dispatch V1.6 and connect to the local database.  The 
   local database must contain a recently refreshed set of data for my Ross terminal.  
   So that I can dispatch with  my customer list, trucking routes and drivers.

#############################################

Feature  SERVER-BASED DISPATCHER

   As a Server-based Dispatcher
   I need the ability to run Dispatch V1.6 and connect to my Dispatch server.  The 
      server database must contain my Ross terminal's Customer, Route and Driver data.  
	 And the data must be fresh.
   So that I can dispatch with  my customer list, trucking routes and drivers.

#############################################

Feature  STANDARD USER

   As a Standard User
   I need the ablity to run: ROADVISION (via Remote Login-RDP), Email, and other applications 
   So that I can function as a Ross employee.

#############################################

Feature HOT SPARE WORKSTATION 

   As a  Windows PC (server or workstation)
   I need Windows installed and a database; and users; and applications installed
   So that I can support Ross users, Dispatch 1.6 operators and/or Comet Tracker users
   So that LIne Hauls can deliver me to replace a failed workstation

#############################################

Feature  RDP USER

   As an  RDP User
   I need the ability to create and use an RDP remote session.
   So that I can interact with RoadVision

#############################################

Feature  SCAN STATION USER

   As a  Scat Station User 
   I need a workstation connected to a scanning device with driver software installed. 
   So that NH data entry operators can read the barcode, validate the 
     Waybill data fields and enter Waybill into RoadVision.

#############################################

Feature  STANDARD USER

   As a Standard User
   I need the ablity to run: ROADVISION (via Remote Login-RDP), Email, and other applications 
   So that I can function as a Ross employee.

#############################################

Feature  WAYBILL CREATOR

   As a  Waybill Creator (scanner operator)
   I need the ability to scan a paper WayBill and send it to the NH terminal for data entry and processing.
   So that NH data entry operators can read the barcode, 
    validate the Waybill data fields 
	and enter Waybill into RoadVision.

#############################################
